# DARREL AUSTERO

FREELANCER



Skype Name live:darrelwork2014



darrelwork2022@yahoo.com



Lutao, Bacong Neg. Or. Philippines

# **PROFILE**

I am a qualified and professional freelancer with five years of experience in customer service. Also, I have experience as a real estate virtual assistant and a WordPress web developer. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

# SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Social Media Management
- Photo and Video Editing
- WordPress Web Development
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

## EXPERIENCE

## **WORDPRESS WEB DEVELOPER**

Freelancer

2021- Present

 Create and design WordPress websites. Setup and activate plugins, do system integration and make progress reports.

## **REAL ESTATE VIRTUAL ASSISTANT**

Jason Pugao Keller-Williams

2020-2021

 Edit photos of listings, create marketing emails in mailchimp, post listings in social media platforms, create engagement posts in social media platforms.

## **CUSTOMER SERVICE REP**

**CONVERGYS** 

2014-2019

• Assist customers through phone channel.

# CHARACTER REFERENCE

Carlston Grefalde - WebDeveloper carlstongrefalde@gmail.com

# EDUCATION

#### **SECONDARY SCHOOL**

San Miguel National High School 1998 - 2002

### **DIPLOMA OF TECHNOLOGY**

Negros Oriental State University 2002 - 2005